在接下来的几节中，我想谈谈所有面临的一些重大挑战
In the next few sections, I want to talk about some of the big challenges that confront all
我们作为一个社会，作为一个民族。我们面临的挑战的根本原因是
of us as a society, as a people. The root cause of the challenges that confront us are
基本上是世界人口的增长。在此图中，此处显示了三种不同的方案。
essentially the world population growth. In this graph here shows, three different scenarios.
这些被称为中等增长模型，其行星的人口数量最多
These are called medium growth model, which has population of the planet topping out at
到2050年将达到89亿。低增长模式，即人口增长
8.9 billion by the 2050. The low growth model, which sees population
实际上在大约2035年开始下降和相当可怕的高增长
actually starting to decline after about the year 2035 and the rather scary high growth
到2050年，这个地球上有106亿人口的模型。这将是必要的
model which sees 10.6 billion people in the planet by the year 2050. It's going to take
几年前，我们可以找出我们所处的特定线路。
a few years before we can work out which of these particular lines we are on.
这个星球上更多人的后果很多。首先，我们需要
The consequences of more people on the planet are many. For a start, we are going to need
再来点吃的。这个星球上还有更多的嘴巴要喂。
more food. There are more mouths to be fed on the planet.
我们需要更多资源。每个人都需要能源等资源
We are going to need more resources. Each person requires resources such as energy to
制造他们需要的物品，无论是住房还是其他种类的商品。我们需要材料
manufacture items that they need whether that's housing or other sorts of goods. We need materials
像金属和石油资源，我们需要水-饮用水和水
like metals and petroleum resources and we need water - water for drinking and also water
用于洗涤和制造用水，这些人需要的所有物品。
for washing and water for manufacturing, all the items that these people require.
最后，还需要更多的交通工具。我们有更多的人
And finally, there is going to need a whole lot more transportation. We have more people
在这个星球上，更多人需要从A点到B点。所有这些资源
in the planet, more people will need to go from point A to point B. All these resources
需要从生产地运输到将要使用的地方。
need to be transported from where they are produced to where they are going to be used.
因此，增加了人员的运输量和人们所需的资源。
So, increased amount of transportation for people and the resources that the people require.